you stop?
All right, let's
do
the
same thing.
Oh
28 years ago, during the second
year of Odin's journey...
My son is born!
Name a Meg! Seaweed!
Fishcake! Meatball! Stop!
I am not naming him after
things you put in Odin!
Our son is peerless among men,
therefore his name must reflect that!
He shall be known as Kozuki Momonosuke.
I'll remind you, you're a wanted man now!
So outside of Wano, you're just
another criminal with a bounty.
If you truly care about Lady
Toki and Lord Momonosuke?
Why don't you consider returning
home where they can be safe?
I am not ready yet.
There is still an answer
I'm searching for.
Please, don't worry, we're all right.
We have strong friends. Still,
it's a pity that these
newspaper things don't give
us any updates on what's
happening back in Wano.
How could there, since no
information ever leaves the country?
It's just like so.
I wonder how the other retainers are.
Eh?
Divisions in the crew?
There's quite a few of us.
So, I think five divisions
should work out fine.
Great idea pops. I like it.
Oh, let me be a commander,
please me to Odin You will serve
as the second division commander.
Well, I'm not so sure that I
do it.
Justice fate brought us to Whitebeard.
So did it bring the other crew members
listen We're not fishermen or merchants.
We're pirates. They don't care
Please, I've got nowhere else to go.
Hey, stop!
What's your name, kid?
It's, uh, teach, sir.
Fine then, come aboard.
Thank you so much, sir.
Another orphan, it seems?
Did you see that?
Something's flying over
there! Ha ha ha! Ah!
No matter how far we sail,
I desire to see more.
Command your way!
We have the Scouper!
I don't know how to end an
adventure like this once it's begun.
Meanwhile, in the land of Wano...
Special report!
Terrible news!
Lord Tsukiyaki is critically ill!
His end may be close at hand!
Shogun's no!
The country faced a serious crisis,
and so the daimyos from
each region in the land of
Wano came to the flower capital
to meet with the Shogun.
I want Odin to succeed me.
He must be the next Shogun.
Of course, my lord.
Just as you wish.
However, since Odin is not here with us,
I must assign a proxy to take
his place for the time being.
I fear that before he returns,
something unfortunate may befall me.
I have chosen this man, who Odin
treated like a little brother.
Kurozumi Orochi.
Orochi?
What's going on here?
Odin treated him like a
brother, he says. Really?
I am grateful.
You have given me an opportunity
to clear the Kurozumi name.
I owe a great debt to Lord Sukiyaki for
this and to Lord Odin for his kindness.
I will atone for my grandfather's
mistakes as best I can.
I shall humbly prepare the throne for
Lord Odin so that he may ascend someday.
I will be but a puppet upon that seat.
Awaiting Lord Odin's return.
So I beg for your aid and
your guidance until then!
You're a Kurozumi, are you?
Why didn't you tell me?
So sorry.
I can see the future.
I see you.
You will become the show guy.
You're out of your mind, lady.
Tell me who you are right now.
Your grandfather, do you know how he died?
Well, I don't know the details, but I
was told he committed sepulchral a lie.
He was killed by the kozookis, what but
he committed some kind of crime, right?
It was a struggle for political
power struggle for power;
whoever stands at the
top writes the rules.
His actions were only called
a crime because he lost!
The previous Kozuki shogun
had a weakness, you see.
Try as he might, he couldn't sire a child.
He had no heir!
This read uncertainty among the five
daimyos serving under the Kozuki clan.
Suddenly, it was unclear who
would be the next shogun.
Why it should be me, they all thought.
But your grandfather did more than think.
He was making preparations.
And by making preparations, I mean he was
poisoning those rival daimyos one by one.
He made it look like an inside job,
as if each region had its
own struggle for power.
The shogun,
Rocket with grief over the death of
his loyal daimyos, eventually fell ill.
Everything was going according to plan.
But just when it seemed that his ambitions
would be realized, disaster struck!
Oh, the Shogun got what he needed
at last, an heir, Kozuki Tsukiyaki!
A miracle!
The clan has been saved!
Kozuki Tsukiyaki!
Oh, your grandfather was so close.
But not only was his plan
thwarted, it was exposed.
He was brought low.
They forced him to commit seppuku.
Then the clan lost everything.
Their territory, property,
and power was stolen.
People despised the name Kurozumi.
The clan was tossed in the
streets made lower than dirt.
Tell me whose fault is that?
Who is to blame for
your misery and poverty?
Not your grandfather who
wanted the best for his family?
When did it all go wrong?
When he was born.
Go, Tsuki-Suki-Aki.
That's right.
If he was never born, you surely
would have become the Shogun someday.
Shogun Orochi, I love you.
Yes, we all do.
You're just the best.
Oh, Shogun.
You're too much, girls.
Really? Shogun?
But of course.
Oh, it's just galling, isn't it?
Wait, don't tell me you're like me.
Is that why you care?
Because you're a Kurozumi, too?
Who I am is of no importance
anymore, don't you understand?
I was out of the country for years.
It's been a terrible ordeal.
Now watch very closely.
Ah!
You stole my face!
What you just witnessed is the
power of the clone clone fruit.
And there's more where that came from.
Do as I bid, and I'll give you power, too.
The power you need to become shogun.
I'll do whatever you want. Tell me.
The first step is to raise
money and produce weapons.
The craftsmen in the land
of Wano possess great skill.
Using weapons as leverage, you can gain
powerful backers from across the seas.
I understand.
My name is Orochi.
I'll accept any work that you can provide.
My entire family has fallen ill, so if I
don't work, I fear that they'll all starve.
I see.
You have my sympathy.
We'll work something out.
Lord Yasui!
What's that?
You said Odinji disappeared. Yes.
Also,
I don't know if it's a coincidence or not,
but it appears your safe
has been emptied out. What?
The money is gone, too.
Didn't I meet you at Yasu's
place a while back? Yes, yes.
The name is Orochi.
Lord Yasui has already helped me so much.
I could never borrow money from him.
Fair enough.
You can count on me.
Lord, wait.
Thank you so much, sir.
I need money. Again?
I need money! Again?
Please let me money.
I can pay you back for sure this time.
You have my word.
I beg of you.
My Lord Odin, I'll remind you.
Our own finances are not
exactly in immaculate shape.
But he said he'd pay it back, right?
Odin, you've come with no retainers.
Why are you here?
Could you please let this
fellow stay here a while?
He works hard and he's
good at preparing medicine.
He is like a little brother to me.
My name is Orochi.
Everyone, take good care of Orochi for me.
As you wish, my lord.
Kyo-kyo-kyo!
The Shogun Sukiyaki, I've done it.
I've clawed my way up to the top.
Stay with us, Lord Sukiyaki.
You must be strong.
Hang on, please.
We're here with you.
If I cannot overcome this
illness, carry on in my place.
Certainly, I'll do my best.
Orochi will need your help.
I ask that you support
him as best you can. Yes.
Oh, Lord Tsukiyaki, we'd
better get you a doctor.
We'll be back shortly.
Help!
We need a physician!
Anyone!
Lord Tsukiyaki, please don't leave us.
We need you.
I leave this land in your hands, Orochi!
It's far too early to say
such a thing, my lord!
I said you'd become
the Shogun, didn't die!
The land of Wado was seized
with great sadness as news
of Shogun Sukiyaki's death
spread across the country.
One day in the fourth
year of Odin's journey.
Look at that!
Oh, they're going crazy!
What happened?
I've never seen fish act like this before.
You think a natural disaster is coming?
It seems like they're all
headed away from that island.
You're right.
You bet some kind of
giant monster lives there.
Marco, go check it out. What?
Did it spoil the surprise?
No, thank you.
Oi, oi.
I'll protect you and your big brother.
We're gonna go, aren't we?
Hmm.
Of course we are.
You ready? Yeah!
What's going on here?
Even the tough-looking
animals are running away.
Something is out there.
Something's strong.
If you guys want to catch me that bad,
you better bring Garper Sengoku next time.
Fighting you is no sport at all.
Captain!
The Whitebeard's ship just showed up.
I think they know we're here.
Looks like they're on the
other side of the island.
We just finished one fight, Roger.
What now, white beard?
Huh, haven't seen him in quite a while.
If the birds are taken off,
he must have come ashore all right.
Let's have a bout then?
You can only risk death
while you're still alive!
My end is coming soon after all.
Odds are, this is the last time you and
I will ever cross paths, white beard.
There's some weird guy in
robes who's running crazy fast!
A samurai!
He's here too, huh?
Lucky me!
All of you are running too slow!
I think you're too fast, actually!
I'm supposed to blunder
their treasure first, right?
This is totally different
than our usual battles!
The Roger Pirates are seriously tough!
He's not listening at all!
Koyanku!
Koyanku! Yes!
He's as strong as they say he is.
I think he's wreaked enough
havoc for now. I agree.
Cap 'n, Rayleigh, wait! Huh? Allow me.
I'd sure hate to see my crew get hurt.
You just wanna fight him.
I smell a beast.
Ahoy there, samurai!
Divine Departure!
What in the hell was that?
Sit up, pal.
We can't have that.
There you are.
I'm not sure what you're doing.
You're looking well, Roger.
Good to see you.
How many years has it been, Newgate?
Too many, I say.
Now hand over all you've got!
Let's go!
It is a clash between the
greatest crews of the age.
The Roger Pirates versus
the Whitebeard Pirates.
The intense battle lasted for
three days and three nights.
Time to get serious.
Sorry kid, but I'm always serious.
Tough break!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
How's three boxes of
turkey for one barrel?
Good deal!
I like this shirt!
Where did you find this one?
Let me have more! Hold it!
It took too much!
It's got to be an even exchange, buddy.
All right, fine.
Got something else to fork
over, then? You betcha.
Looks like the pillaging
has become a gift exchange.
Who are those two? Apprentices?
Ah, yeah, they have been
tagging along for a while now.
Kind of puny, if you ask me.
But look at those faces.
They look like hardened old vets.
Shanks, look over there. What is it?
Do you see that guy?
The mean-looking one
with the dumb lid? Yeah.
I heard he didn't sleep during the ceasefire
last night or the night before either.
Hmm?
Yeah, so?
Probably just showing off.
Are you stupid?
It's not normal.
From what I hear, he's never
slept a day in his life.
Huh?
Didn't know people could do that.
Wow, cool.
He must get to have double the fun.
Fun, he says.
Yeah, that guy looks
like a barrel of laughs.
He's a monster!
You think?
So, Odin, can you make
any sense of this text?
Indeed, I can read it.
But you must tell me why
you possess this script.
Knowledge of these writings
has been passed down from
generation to generation
exclusively in the Kozuki clan.
It all started 13 years ago.
We landed at the destination
of the final Log Pose.
And arrived at a place no man
had ever set foot upon before,?
Lodestar Island.
We disembarked with a smile.
But our victory was an empty one!
because we learned that it
wasn't the final island.
The Log Pose needles were spinning out
of control, refusing to guide us further.
That's when it dawned on me!
There was one last destination!
And once I visit there,
I will be the first person to
travel the entirety of the world!
Look at this.
These letters will show me the way.
They're rubbings that my crew
and I took from a huge red stone.
There are four of those stones out there,
and the world government has always
forbidden anyone from deciphering them.
They're called pony glyphs, you see.
I assumed they were just cultural relics.
But as it turns out,
they're part of a map.
That reveals the location of
the last legendary island.
Seems odd the government
prohibits us from looking into it.
There must be a vast treasure there.
How could I possibly resist?
The crew who finds it
will become the greatest
pirates in the world So let's
get out there, shall we?
The greatest?
So, then, we've got a
lot to discuss, don't we?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I was frozen stiff.
For the second time that
day, I found myself stunned.
Who was this fellow?
Believing in old fairy tales now?
You sound like a child, Roger.
But I'm being completely
serious here, Newgate.
Please.
Just for one year,
allow me to borrow Odin.
It's all that I'm asking.
I need that man.
With him, I can find the last island.
Hey, don't I get a say in any of this!
Please, Newgate.
I am begging you.
Captain, what are you doing?
Get on your feet!
He's our enemy!
Why would you bow your head like that?
Have a bit of dignity, man!
I need you, Odin.
You must join us!
I only ask for a year of your time.
I Forbidden!
Roger, are you trying to
steal my family away from me?
I felt a bolt of excitement
shoot down my spine.
Why is it that only the
Kozuki can read those letters?
Was it fate that brought
me together with this man?
Before I knew it, the words were
leaving my mouth without restraint.
Please, White Kashi, I want to go.
Will you please permit me?
It would be a dream to see
the last island for myself.
He's annoyed.
Of course I'm annoyed, you idiot!
How can you do this?
We're practically like brothers It
will only be a year, White Kashi.
I beg you!
You better take care of yourself.
I shall.
We're going to stay with the crew.
We've grown quite fond of this ship.
But we'll be waiting for you, won't we?
Hmm do as you please your full-fledged
pirates now after all
it's your choice to make
He's leaving pops aren't
you gonna send him off
Roger left behind all his
ship's cargo as a thank you
this stuff is worth a fortune
I've never seen so much food
What?
Give it back! Now!
They need it more than we do, you morons!
Don't you dare let
Odin's family go hungry!
Put that back on their ship immediately!
I won't say it twice!
Yes, sir! Right away!
Goodbye, Lord Odin!
Goodbye, everyone!
I'll be back!
You better make all of
us proud, all right?
Get yourself!
Can't wait to hear the stories!
Have fun up there! See ya!
Be safe, all of you!
It was the second act
of my life as a pirate.
A new adventure had begun.
White Kashi is a great man,
but Roger is remarkable, too.
I'm lucky to have met them both!
Oh, what a sweet little pea you are.
Whoopsie-doodle.
I haven't held a baby in a long time.
You know, it reminds me of the old days.
Momonosuke and Hiyori, huh?
Ah, baby. My cat smiles.
Wee!
That's my girl.
Captain Roger, sir!
We got a stowaway!
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Dog Storm!
Cat Viper!
Why are you here?
Well, why not?
We figured we'd have more fun being
with you, Karoo, on your travels.
The dog and the cat have disappeared!
Damn it!
Those two!
Listen, the only reason you're here is
because you can decipher those poneglyphs.
Nothing more, understand?
Next up, I need radishes!
Thief, get back here!
Oh, captain's gonna kick his butt.
Odin, don't mess with the locals!
I need to get more ingredients.
Just what do you need them for?
You see the balls on this guy?
Wait, are we in a lawless land?
Are you seeing this, Skobod? I am.
So they aren't civilians, after all.
Odin!
Did that really just happen?
Holy crap!
You're okay!
That was awesome!
So, I guess since they're not civilians...
They're fair game.
Are you ready?
Indeed.
I still need some cow, what's it for?
To make a delicious broth.
Here a weirdo, all right, enough
of that mess—these guys up!
up
Go, Odin, go!
Reddish and fried tofu.
Some fish, cakes, and eggs, too.
One, two, and three.
Eat it up for me.
Don't let the whole pot spoil.
I'm old and born to boil.
Hmm?
Are you not feeling well? I'm fine.
Nothing to worry about.
What do you mean, nothing to worry about?
Best-case scenario, he's
got a year or so to live.
Gotta catch the wind in
my sails while I can.
Here goes!
That's the knock-up stream ahead!
We're dead!
An island?
No way!
The Sky Island!
We gladly welcome you,
people from the Blue Sea!
The world is so much
faster than I had imagined.
Not even the gods could have
predicted people living in the clouds!
That fool takes ten
years to master a waiver.
Run for your lives!
This is it!
The City of Gold, Shandora! Wow.
I found it!
All the way up here!
That must be it.
Shandora's Grand Belfry.
That thing's pure gold!
How do we haul it back, Captain?
No time for that.
Tell you what, you can come get
it when you're a captain yourself.
Sound good, Boogie?
Can we break off a little piece at least?
The voice is echoing within the
stoner's throng, so it was easy to find.
It's speaking of a great power, isn't it?
The inscription tells you a weapon
named Poseidon. Interesting.
Odin, you're able to write in
this script as well, aren't you?
Yes, of course.
Carve this message!
It's hard to believe Roger is
nearing the end of his life.
He carries on this
quest with such urgency.
I must help him see it to its conclusion.
Like this, Captain!
That should do it! Nice work.
I made it here,
and I will guide this passage all the
way to the farthest ends of the world.
The stormiest seas will not stop me.
I must see it, Raja.
Show me the final chapter of the
adventure you've devoted your life to.
Well, boys, let's go back
to the blue scene! Yeah!